the internet lost its last night over
some salacious new gossip generated by
BuzzFeed about president-elect Donald
Trump the explosive leak is unverified
uh we don't know if it's true now I have
to say uh we were working last night
when this broke I didn't really get all
the details I'm I'm really busy but I
honestly don't see what the big deal is
everybody loves The Golden Girls what is
the
problem it's
especially what's the big
deal yeah right
oh and if they're peeing on you even
better well then at a press conference
this morning Trump confirmed via
catchphrase that his sons will be
running his
companies I hope at the end of eight
years I'll come back and I'll say oh you
did a good job otherwise if they do a
bad job I'll say You're
Fired he did there the thing he said on
the thing he
also he also promised reporters his
inauguration would be very very elegant
uh instead of popular a listers an
artist that millions of people would be
interested in seeing his planner said
he'll be surrounded with soft sensuality
a soft sensuality I don't know maybe
like a nice romantic dinner at home with
Mike hucke and a velvet robe that very
soft and sensual uh don't neglect the
huckabees uh comedians with all this
craziness surrounding our golden leader
how exactly is Trump's inauguration
going to be elegant Emily uh he's going
to swear around on a solid gold Bible
That's encrusted in Swarovski Crystals
but it'll be the size of you know like a
cereal box you get it a diner so that uh
you know so that is his little hand
looks real big yeah okay points points
Matt kersen uh it'll smell like the
finest asparagus yes points points
Reese thanks
everybody yes I'm so sorry it's must
have been hard for you to start talking
from that thunderous round of a
what's we've got a good four years ahead
of us I think this large red button will
uh launch my fireworks display
okay
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh